Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents, 1927-1974
5609
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB); Ross, Philip
459 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Labor relation records.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ross, Philip.; United States. National Labor Relations Board.; A.P.W. Products Company; Ame Brick Company; Advance Specialty Company; Adams Engineering Co., Inc.; Air Control Products, Inc.; Albany Novelty Corp.; Alco Packing Company; Allen & Calhoun General Contractor, Inc.; Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America. Division 1133; American Masonry & Plastering, Inc.; Anderson Construction Corporation; Apex Linen Service; Arnold Equipment Corporation; Assabet River Valley Lodge 2199; Avco-Everett Research Laboratory; Bangor Shoe Mfg. Co., Inc.; Banner Supply Company; Barker's East Main Corp.; Bay Door Corporation; Benjamin Electric Mfg. Company; Benton and Company, Inc.; Berkline Corporation; Bevento Sand & Gravel Com.; Bohn Aluminum and Brass Corporation; Bowman Transportation, Inc.; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company); Brock and Blevins Company; Brook Farm Foods, Inc.; Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America; Budow Machine & Manufacturing Company; Burgess-Norton Company; Cabinets, Inc.; Camp Concrete Rock Company; Campbell-Lowrie Lautermilch Corporation; Carpenters District Council of Kansas City; Carrier Corporations; Cecil Holland Ford, Inc.; Central Connecticut Broadcasting Company, Inc.; Edward Chadderton Trucking Company; Chaplin-Fulton Manufacturing Company; Charlton Press, Inc.; Chemline Corporation; Citrus Products Co-Op; Clearwater Roofing Company; Color Corporation of America; Concrete Products, Inc.; Cone Brothers Contracting Company; Concrete Forms Corporation; Continental Can Company; Copper's Express, Inc.; Contra Costa Times; Crusader-Lancer Corp.; Darling Shop of Meadville, Inc.; Dixie Ohio Express, Inc.; Derby Coal & Oil Co., Inc.; Dinker Tutwiler Hotel; Dole Valve Company; Dormeyer Industries; Duval Engineering & Contracting Company; Elgin Import Motors, Inc.; Enterprise Department Stores, Inc.; Fairbanks Morse and Company; Fields, Edward & Co.; Florida Cities Bus Company; Florida Crushed Stone Company; Florida Publishing Company; Florida Sugar Corporation; Food Machinery and Chemical Corporation; Fork Mountain Mining Company; General Electric Company; Giffen Industries, Inc.; Glass Arts, Inc.; John L. Goss Corporation; Gulf Florida Terminal Co., Inc.; Fletcher Aviation Company; Food Fair Stores, Inc.; Franzier Heating & Air Conditioning Company; Frito-Lay, Inc.; J.W. Fuller Tamping Company; Galloway Manufacturing Corporation; General Armature and Manufacturing Company; General Expressways, Inc.; General Motors Corporation. b Chevrolet Motor Division; General Window Corporation; George A. Fuller Company; Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the U.S. & Canada. b Local 169; Glass-Tile Industries, Inc.; Globe Company (Cincinnati, Ohio); Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company; Great Eastern Color Lithographic Corp.; Hampden Brass & Aluminum Company, Inc.; Healzer Cartage Company; Heywood Wakefield Company of Tennessee; Hirsh Manufacturing Company; Hotel Bankhead Corporation; Hotpoint; Howard Hall Company, Inc.; Huber & Huber Motor Express, Inc.; Hudson Pulp and Paper Corporation; Independent Workers Union of Florida; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. b Local 412; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. b Local 41; International Hod Carriers', Building, and Common Laborers' Union of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; J.M. Fields; J. & S. Dillon & Sons Stores Co., Inc.; Jacksonville Journal Company; Jehle Brothers Inc.; Ken Lee, Inc.; Kessel Kurz & Root Company; Koppers Company; Lakeland Cement Company; Liberty Powder Defense Corporation; Lincoln Drug Comapny, Inc.; International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union. b Local 1759; Loungerie, Inc.; Lowell Sun Publishing Company; Lowes Grand Theatre; International Association of Machinists. Local 115; Martin Oil Service Inc.; Master Packaging, Inc.; Merrill Transport Company; Meyers Heating & Appliances Company; Midwestern Industries Corporation; Miller Manufacturing Company, Inc.; Montgomery Ward; Moore Dry Kiln Company; Murphy Company; Myers Ceramic Products Company; National Cabinet Corporation; National Casket Company; National Clothes Pin Company; National Distillers and Chemical Corporation; National Pool Equipment Company; Omega Food Products, Inc.; Patt Engineering & Mfg. Co.; Peoples Gas System, Inc.; Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc.; Pittsburgh Standard Conduit Company; Polo Products Company; Poray, Inc.; Port Everglade Towing Company; Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Division of United Aircraft Corporation; Radiaphone Company, Inc.; Ralph L. Smith Lumber Company; Raymond Diehl Company; Raytheon Manufacturing Company; Reliable Manufacturing Company; Riverdaly Plating & Heat Treating Company; Roddy Manufacturing Company; Royal Aluminum, Inc.; S.N. Nielsen Company; S.S. Jacobs Compnay; Safeway Stores, Inc.; Salerno-Megowen Biscuit Company; Sari Sue Inc.; Sears, Roebuck and Company; Select Foods, Inc.; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association; Sheridan Silver Col., Inc.; Sidles Company; Sigmund Transfer Company; Sky Line Industries; Southern Chemical Cotton Company; Sparton Abrasive Co., Inc.; Specialty Machine Comapny, Inc.; Standard Oil Company of California; Standard Oil Company (Indiana); Spee Dee Service Systems, Inc.; Stereo Corporation of America; Sterling Drum Company; Sunbeam Lighting Company, Inc.; Tampa Marine Shipbuilding Company; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; Tennant Brothers; Tiffany Tile Corporation; Topps Kerrmill, Inc.; Torrington Company; Transcontinental Bus System, Inc.; Tropical Awning Windo & Jalousie Company; True Temper Corporation; Trumbull Asphalt Company of Delaware; Tucker Aluminum Products, Inc.; Tumpane Contracting Company; United Mine Workers of America; United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers' Association; United States Concrete Pipe; United States Steel Corporation; United Steelworkers of America; United Wire & Supply Corporation; Universal Delta; Vernon Sportservice Inc.; Veterans Thrift Store; Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corporation; Walnut Kernel; Wate, Inc.; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; Western Electric Company; Western Massachusetts Electric Company; Wilson and Toomer Fertilizer Company; Wilson Specialties Co., Inc.; Winchester Electronis, Incorporated Pyne Molding, Incorporated; Winston & Green; Young Spring & Wire Corporation
Subjects:
Concrete products industry
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5541: Philip Taft Papers
5619/016: ACTWU Research Department Files
5619/045: ACTWU New England Regional Joint Board Records
5883: Frank McCulloch Papers
/3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers
/3012: Alice Cook Papers
/3036: Robert Raimon Papers
/3051: Albert Martin Papers
/4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers
/4040: George H. Hildebrand Papers
/4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files
/4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes
/4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs
/4064: Kurt Hanslowe Papers
/4073: James O. Morris Office Files
/4085: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers
/4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes
/4117 P: ILR School Photographs
/4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files
/4148: George W. Brooks Additional Papers
/4162: Kheel Center Additional Special Projects Files
/4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files
/4166 AV: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Audio-Visual Materials
/4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files
/4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files
/4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence
/4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files
/4256: ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials
/4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files
/4349: James A. Gross Collections
5011: Morton Singer Papers
5016: Cornell University Union Representation Material
CONTAINER LIST
- 21-CA-4739-1; Kessel, Kurtz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Anaheim, California
- 21-CA-4739-2; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 21-CA-4739-3; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 21-CA-4739-4; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 21-CA-4739-5; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 21-CA-4739-6 Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 21-CA-4739-7; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 21-CA-4739-8; Kessel Kurz & Root Company, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 17-CA-2234; Safeway Stores, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Omaha, Nebraska
- 17-CA-2235; Atlantic Mills Discount Dept. Store, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  A. M. Servicing Corp of Raytown, Missouri
- 12-CA-2236; Safeway Bleach Plant, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Hutchinson, Kansas
- 17-CA-2237; Rock Island Lumber Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Great Bend, Kansas
- 17-CA-2238; C.F. Bender Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Kansas City, Kansas
- 17-CA-2239; Duo Bed Corporation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Wichita, Kansas
- 17-CA-2240; Sterling Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 17-CA-2242; Fruhauf Southwest Garment Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 17-CA-2243; F.M. Stamper Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Macon, Missouri
- 17-CA-2244; Electra Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Independence, Kansas
- 17-CA-2245; Ready-Mix Concrete Co of Lawrence, Kansas, INC., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Lawrence, Kansas
- 17-CA-2246; Gold Bond Poultry, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 17-CA-2247; Dietzgen of Kansas (Formerly Kansas Blue Print Co.), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 17-CA-2248; Willard Stockmen, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Jefferson City, Missouri
- 17-CA-2249; United States Check Book Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Omaha, NE
- 17-CA-2250; E.A. Martin Machinery Co., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Springfield, Missouri
- 17-CA-2251; Enterprise Tool & Die, INC., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Mt. Vernon, Missouri
- 17-CA-2254 Martin K. Eby Construction Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Nebraska City, Nebraska
- 17-CA-2255; Noah Blucord, d/b/a Precision Model Makers & Carvers, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Haysville, Kansas
- 17-CA-2256; Holiday Manufacturing Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Grand Island, Nebraska
- 17-CA-2257; Gravely Tractors (Division Studebaker Corp), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Fort Scott, Kansas
- 17-CA-2258; Inter-Collegiate Press, INC, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Mission, Kansas
- 17-CA-2259; Erickson Transport Corp., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- 17-CA-2260; Safeway Bleach Plant, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 17-CA-2260; Statements and Exhibits; Safeway Bleach Plant, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 17-CA-2261, Royal McBee Typewriter Corp., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 17-CA-2262; Clark Printing Company, INC, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Kansas City, Missouri
- 17-CA-2263; Dietzgen of Kansas (formerly Kansas Blue Print Co.), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- 17-CA-2265; Springday Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- 17-CA-2266; Airlite Plastics Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- 17-CA-2267; Mid-Continent Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Rich Hill, Missouri
- 17-CA-2268; King Transfer, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- 17-CA-2269; R & C Packing Co., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- 17-CA-2270; A Boss Chain, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- 17-CA-2271; Townhouse Motor Hotel, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- 17-CA-2274; Lackland Plating Company, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Independence, Missouri
- 1-CA-2767; Scott Paper Company Hollingsworth & Whitney Div., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Winslow, Maine
- 1-CA-2772; Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Boston, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-22771; I. Schnierson & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Fall River, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2762; Arcade Malleable Iron Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Worcester, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2761; Argonne Worsted Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Woonsocket, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2759; Union Fabric Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Derby, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2752; Prophylactic Brush Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Florence, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2751; I. Schneierson & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1-CA-2677; Enterprise Department Stores, Inc. d/b/a J.M. Fields Discount Stores, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Medford, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2849; National Clothes Pint Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Montpelier, Vermont
- 1-CA-2529; Regal Shoe Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Whitman, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2547; Cities Service Oil Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  New York, New York
- 1-CA-2586; Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 1-CA-2778; Emery Waterhouse Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Manchester, New Hampshire
- 1-CA-2861; Robinson Metals Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 1-CA-2865; Fells Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Allston, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2866; Boston Gas Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- 1-CA-2867; Abington Textile Machinery, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  No. Abington, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2868; REX Coat & Suit Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Central Falls, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2848; Central Beef Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- 1-CA-2854; Hampden Coal & Oil Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Springfield, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2853; Gonic Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Gonic, New Hampshire
- 1-CA-2847; Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp., Willimantic Division, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Willimantic, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2846; Fall River & New Bedford Express Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 1-CA-2844; Nigro Freight Lines, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Farmington, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2843; United Television Company of New Hampshire, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 1-CA-2869; Trailways of New England, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- 1-CA-2700; Mass. Gear & Tool Company and Geartronics Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Woburn, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2665; Uncas MFG. Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Providence, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2996; Queen Plastics, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- 1-CA-2975; Fox & Ginn, Inc., and Fox & Ginn Moving & Storage CO., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Portland, Maine
- 1-CA-2976; Warwick Ginger Ale Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  West Warwick, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2977; Eastern Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Newton, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2978; Tubular Rivet & Stud Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Wollaston, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2966; Raytheon Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Quincy, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2967; United States Rubber Company NY, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Chicopee Falls, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2968; General Electric Co., Clock & Timer Div., Telechron Dept., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- 1-CA-2969; Northeast Tool & Engineering Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- 1-CA-2930; Mansfield Bleachery, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Mansfield, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2950; Atlantic Register Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  Waltham, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2949; Allied Chemical Coating, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  Lynn, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2943; Capital Distributing Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- 1-CA-2942; Brockton Taunton Gas Company, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  Brockton, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2939; Koppel Photo Engraving Company Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  New Haven, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2960; F.N. Calderwood Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- 1-CA-2958; Artgold Leather Goods Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  Roslindale, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2955; Milliken Tomlinson Co, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- 1-CA-2941; Chemical Development Corporation, Devcon Corporation, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  Danvers, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2937; Capitol Dist. Co., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- 1-CA-2936; Capitol Broadcasting Incorporated, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  Hartford, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2935; H. Goldman Inc. & Humboldt Storage Warehouse, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  Roxbury, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2934; Massachusetts Hotel Corporation et al, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- 1-CA-2959; Sheridan Silver Co., Inc. Wilson Specialties Co, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  Taunton, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2991; Cooper's Express, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  Lawrence, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2990; Cooper's Express, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- 1-CA-2989; Cooper's Express, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- 1-CA-2988; Cooper's Express, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- 1-CA-2987; Cooper's Express Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- 1-CA-2986; United States Rubber Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- 1-CA-2985; Allied Polymer Corp., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- 1-CA-2984; Baxter Woolen Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  East Rochester, New Hampshire
- 1-CA-2965; Rijack Service, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- 1-CA-2964; New England Electronic Components, Inc. & Holyoke Institute of Research, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  Holyoke, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2963 Pinkerton National Detective Agency Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  Boston 10, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2962; Edgerton Germeshausen and Grier, Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- 1-CA-2961; Rockingham Park Race Track, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  Salem Depot, New Hampshire
- 1-CA-2932; A.G. Spalding & Bros., Inc., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  Chicopee, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2818; Charlton Press, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 1-CA-2817; Charlton Press, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 1-CA-2816; Charlton Press, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 1-CA-2815; Charlton Press, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 1-CA-2819; Charlton Press, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 1-CA-2836; National Clothes Pin Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 1-CA-2822; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Div. of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Maynard, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2821; Socony Mobil Oil Co., Inc. Eastern Pipe Lines Div., Prov. Hartford Dist. Pipe Line, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  East Douglas, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2823; CBS-Hytron, Division of Columbia Broadcasting System, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 1-CA-2820; Nigro Freight Lines, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 1-CA-2824; National Clothes Pin Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 1-CA-2825; National Clothes Pin Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 1-CA-2826; Robert Sportswear Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Lowell, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2827; Western Pork Packers, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 1-CA-2828; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 1-CA-2802; Motor Sales Company of New Bedford, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  New Bedford, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2803; New Bedford Storage Warehouse Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 1-CA-2829; National Clothes Pin Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 1-CA-2830; A. F. Public over & Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 1-CA-2832; H. A. Miller Shoe Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 1-CA-2833; National Clothes Pin Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1-CA-2834; Revere Racing Association Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Revere, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2835; H. Tabenken & Co. Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Veazie, Maine
- 1-CA-2806; Van Norman Machine Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- 1-CA-2808; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- 1-CA-2807; Bradley-Sun Corporation ( Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 1-CA-2809; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- 1-CA-2810; Bradley-Sun Corporation Division of the American Can Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 1-CA-2811; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 1-CA-2812; Charles Dowd Box Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- 1-CA-2813; Bradley-Sun Corporation (Division of American Can Company), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- 1-CA-2814; Normandy Print Works, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 1-CA-2792; Island Plastic Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- 1-CA-2793; Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- 1-CA-2794; Korber Hats, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- 1-CA-2797; Bancroft Tissue Mills, Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Bancroft, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2799; Imperial Upholstery Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- 1-CA-2801; Bethlehem Steel Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- 1-CA-2779; Southington Hardware, Division of Pittsburgh Screw and Bolt Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Southington, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2783; General Electric Telechron Dept. Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 1-CA-2784; Gilbane Building Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Providence, R.I.
- 1-CA-2785; Mayflower Doughnut Corp., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 1-CA-2786; Western Massachusetts Electric Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 1-CA-2788; Western Massachusetts Electric Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 1-CA-2789; Great Eastern Manufacturing Corporation, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Springfield, Vermont
- 1-CA-2773; Diamond Ginger Ale, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Waterbury, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2760; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Shrewsbury, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2763; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 1-CA-2764; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 1-CA-2765; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 1-CA-2766; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1-CA-2755; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 1-CA-2745; Lisson-Melen Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 1-CA-2768; H. E. Fletcher Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  West Chelmsford, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2747; New England Office Partition & Fixture Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 1-CA-2743; Charles Dowd Box Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 1-CA-2746; New England Office Partition&; Fixture Co. Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 1-CA-2776; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- 1-CA-2754; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 1-CA-2840; Portland Sportswear Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- 1-CA-2839; United Aircraft Corp. Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Div., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  North Haven, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2974; General Electric Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Somersworth, New Hampshire
- 1-CA-2971; Lorell Printing Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  South Boston 27, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2973; Colonial Shoe Ornament Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Haverhill, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2756; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- 1-CA-2757; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- 1-CA-2758; General Expressways, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- 1-CA-2858; Iseli Swiss Screw Machine Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Terryville, Connecticut
- 1-CA-2851; Pfister Aluminum Corporation, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  North Adams, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2860; Rochambeau Worsted Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Manville, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2842; Parks & Woolson Machine Co., Division of Riggs & Lombard, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- 1-CA-2841; National Clothes Pin Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- 1-CA-2870; Bonnar Vawter Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Rockland, Maine
- 1-CA-2859; Blanchard Machine Co., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Cambridge, Massachusetts
- 1-CA-2874; Glass-Tite Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Cranston, Rhode Island
- 1-CA-2875; Frank Amodio & Sons, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 38)